[

Lockdown Privacy](https://lockdownprivacy.com/)

#### **Lockdown Privacy Policy**

Last Updated February 23rd, 2023

Lockdown has a privacy policy for its firewall and a privacy policy for its VPN, depending on which product(s) you're using. Unlike other Privacy Policies, Lockdown's Privacy Policies are _proven_, rather than blind-faith assertions.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [team@lockdownprivacy.com](mailto:terms@lockdownprivacy.com) and we will respond as soon as possible.

#### **Lockdown Firewall Privacy Policy**

Everything Lockdown Firewall does stays on your device, and what you see is literally what you get, and nothing more or less, because that's the way it should be.

Longer Version: Everything Lockdown Firewall does stays on your phone, so no data is transmitted to any of our servers. This can be confirmed by checking the [source code](https://github.com/confirmedcode/Lockdown-iOS), which is 100% open and public for anyone to examine. Lockdown Firewall doesn't use any type of third party analytics, trackers, or APIs, so there's no risk of your data leaking to third parties. This means there's no Google Analytics, no Facebook Pixel, no Mixpanel, Fabric, Mailchimp, etc — nada.

##### Information We Collect

Lockdown Firewall collects nothing. It all stays on your device.

#### **Lockdown VPN Privacy Policy**

Lockdown VPN is powered by our Confirmed VPN, the Openly Operated and fully audited VPN that proves its no-log, no-tracking policies.

Confirmed VPN is certified as Openly Operated, so it is able to provide proof of the privacy claims in this Privacy Policy by using references from its [OpenAudit](https://openaudit.com/lockdownprivacy). Learn more about the [Openly Operated Certification](https://openlyoperated.org/), and read Confirmed VPN's full [Privacy Policy](https://confirmedvpn.com/privacy).

© Confirmed 2023

##### Navigation

##### Legal

##### Other
